fasthighlights.com 2013-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Football Highlights & Goals & Football Videos - GoalsUP

## Privacy Policy

Do you **like this page?**  
Tell your friends this video is awesome!

## Goalsup Privacy Policy

Updated 15/08/2012   
This Privacy Policy describes how Goalsup and its subsidiaries treat personal information when you use our services, including information provided when you use the Goalsup Website. 

### Personal Information

* Non-Account Activity. You can watch videos on Goalsup without having a Goalsup Account. 

* Content Uploaded to Site. Any personal information, photos or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

### Uses

* If you submit personally identifiable information to us through Goalsup, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Goalsup Site, and to process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us. 

* We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Goalsup Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, analyzing, and processing user preferences and trends, as well as user activity and communications.* We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Goalsup Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests. 

**Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Site**   
Goalsup allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Goalsup Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Goalsup Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. 

Goalsup does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Goalsup to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Goalsup Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices.Goalsup’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared withGoalsup is maintained and dealt with by Goalsup in accordance with this privacy policy. 

### More Information

Goalsup adheres to the US Safe Harbor privacy principles. For more information about the Safe Harbor framework or our registration, see the Department of Commerce’s web site. 

For more information you may contact Goalsup through email form available on Goalsup.com
